So when I first came here to
do a Fringe show in this room
Which is three years ago and
the night before my first show I
was supposed to come here
and do a tech rehearsal.
I had no idea what a
fucking tech rehearsal
was I'm like what like if I come on
to this tech rehearsal What are they gonna
ask me like they're gonna ask me questions
about the lighting or something
I'm not really going to know.
I'm not, like, an idiot and
I was really really fretting about it and
like I'm not saying I would have done
this But there was like part
of me was thinking well,
maybe I just won't do this
show then like if I have to go to
this tech rehearsal, I just won't
do this show and It was kind
of because it was humiliating.
It was just me kind of being asked to
do something I didn't know how to do and
of course I turned up and they
said how do you want your lights?
And I was like like a stand-up
stage and they were like,
yeah, what you mean
like that? I was like, yeah, and they
said like do you want to play some music?
I was like, yeah, that was it All
right, so that kind of wasn't a big deal